Chat!
I'm going to be a little more obvious with my clothes and stuff.
I'd like to make a video of us chatting backstage at the end of our two-day talk.
Well...
I worked hard today.
It's not that I'm having a hard time or anything.
It's not that it's hard or anything, it's just that it's hard to speak all day long, isn't it?
I mean, you're talking all the time in the second half of the day.
It's like when your mouth moves before your brain decides what to say.
Like when someone says, "It's your birthday.
I'd say, "Thank you" first.
But me? Like that.
It happens a lot with compliments.
The other day, when I was online...
He told me that he hasn't shaken hands directly with me in a really long time.
I was like, "Oh, thank you.
I was told, "Sorry, we only have a few tickets.
I said, "Oh, I'm so glad!
Oh, man...
That's not "happy"!
I'm happy to go shake hands with you.
I said I'm glad we only have a few tickets.
What?
I'm sorry... but I didn't mean it that way.
I've been told before that I'm like the hottest guy in a thousand years.
Here he comes... in real life.
I said I've seen him so much.
He said he was the hottest guy in a thousand years.
He didn't grin at all. He had a real straight face.
I knew it. He's funny shaking hands.
I know this is a bit of a bitch, but...
Sometimes I take a cab to get around.
The other day I took a cab.
There are drivers who talk to you all the time.
But I have the image that there are many of them in Osaka.But I have this image that Osaka has a lot of people who are about to speak.
In Tokyo, they say a couple of words.
But if I don't get on that much, they don't talk much.
But he talked for the whole 30 minutes.
Basically, he was talking about his personal life.
It was like he cancelled 3 times this morning.
I was really upset.
I didn't think he was going to talk for that long.
I didn't think I was going to talk that long, so the first thing I said was something like, "Well, I'm sorry.
He said, "It's raining today, so you didn't get caught, right?
I said, "Oh yeah, thank God.
And then we just kept talking.
For example, he said I was going to his hometown.
And he said, "This area is my hometown.
Like, "I'll take the local road and get there as soon as possible.
I'm not going to fall for that.
But the driver was a great K-pop singer.
I don't want to speak ill of him here.
I love K-pop.
"It's boring as shit.
I'm serious.
I think your story is more boring than mine.
But it's been a long time coming, really.
But I shouldn't have.
And I just wrote it down right here.
It's so fucked up.
And this isn't really a big deal, but I was on the train the other day, and there were these foreign tourists, like, all Westernized and stuff, and I was standing in the dungeon, and there were four of them sitting here, and they were whispering to each other.
There were four of them sitting here, and they were whispering.
They were totally whispering and whispering about something about me, and I was like, "What?
But I don't know... it's like I don't know what's going on... but I'm scared... what should I do?
I'm sorry for peeking in on your LINE, but those four of them are definitely sending each other messages on the group LINE.
When he popped me on there, the other three laughed hysterically.
It's so scary, isn't it? Like they're laughing at me on LINE to foreign tourists.
What? But I don't know what to make of it, there's nothing weird about it.
I knew when I got off at the end, why he was laughing.I knew why they were laughing when I got off at the end.
It was because the four of us were wearing matching sneakers, and my sneakers were exactly the same as theirs.
That's it.
It was like a really hilarious game.
I guess we all had matching shoes, and maybe one of us
I could see that they were whispering to each other.
Maybe they wanted to take a picture of us with the same shoes.
He wanted to take a picture of us wearing the same shoes as Japanese people he didn't know when he came to Japan.
I took a picture and sent it to the group line, and there was a lot of laughter.
Seriously, they were the exact same color and shape.
We kind of walked off, and the four of them are just now getting off.
I was getting off at Ginza, and I thought, "Oh my God, it's okay, this is happening.
Oh my God, it's okay, this is happening...
Did I tell you what I wanted to tell you?
And like I said before...
Lately, when I've been meeting with the TV crew...
I've been watching youtube, and the staff...
I've been talking about the comment patrol.
I didn't talk about it for TV.
I'm talking about the fans who go out of their way to watch the show and see what I'm talking about.
You say shit like that, don't you?
When they say, "This is funny.
You're a celebrity who doesn't have many business cards.
You can't suddenly say, "Your fans suck.
I'm so nervous.
I'm nervous.
Maybe this youtube story
I might end up talking about it on a nationally televised noon show.
Oh no!
That's why I thought it was a little bit dangerous.
I've got another story out there, but it's too fucking weak.
It's too fucking weak, and that's the water story I just told you.
And just for fun, I'm going to be on TV at noon.
I was talking shit about my fans on TV at noon, and I thought, "Well, that's what I'm supposed to do.
I was talking about water, and they're like, "Oh, good for you.
I'm in trouble, aren't I?I'm in trouble, aren't I?
I don't want to do it.
Comment patrolling is the most common thing people say to me.
When I'm approached at restaurants and other places...
They say, "I love Comment Patrol.
I've been told that a lot today.
I think they're doing it next year.
That's what I mean.
I understand that you have feelings for me.
That's why I want to tell you.
But I don't have a chance or a place to say it.
People might be holding back for a long time.
Maybe they'll come.
Because I'm saying it.
You're saying it for me.
That's the only part that made me feel good.
And the DMs.
I'm sorry if I said I was looking at your DMs.
I don't know, it's just... it's been amazing lately.
I don't know...
I'm getting a lot of them. But as usual, he's still sending me "I'll marry you every day, I love you. He sends it to me every day.
That's great! How long has he been sending them? Wait a minute, I've been sending them since January and they're saying let's get married. I'm graduating and getting married at the same time, and it says let's get married.
Wait a minute! Can you please not decide my graduation and future without my permission? Let's get married.
I'm getting messages saying I had fun today, March 12. Please let there be an event. Isn't nothing the scariest thing of all?
I'll make an announcement on March 12. The talk show is over.
Wait a minute. You mean you can't go to that? Sure. That's not so scary, is it?
Tea drinking? Oh, sure!
They're here. They're here. There you are! I'm having fun today... but I'm going to marry you and I love you. He sends me home every day.
Oh, my God! So, I guess that means he played that ball game, too.
Yes, interesting.
So, I'm very happy to be able to say what I'm into and what I want to say.
Surprisingly, this chit-chat is starting to spread.
I want to buy some Calbis and go home.
undiluted solution
I asked for cherries too early.
All the cherries I got in the box were still yellow and not sweet enough.I got a box of cherries and they were all still yellow and not sweet.
I looked it up and found out that cherries are not a fruit that gets sweeter if you leave them in the box.
It's only when they're picked that they become sweet!
So I looked it up and it turns out that if you put the cherries in Calbis solution and put them in the freezer to cool, they will absorb the Calbis and become sweeter.
The cherries absorb the Calbis and become sweet.
That's what I wanted to do.
On the way home, I wanted to buy
Calbis solution, toilet paper and mentsuyu
I'm taking notes.
Well, that's all for now.
Thank you for your time.
See you soon!